paystack.com 2016-06-28

# Paystack

This Privacy Policy describes your privacy rights regarding Paystack’s (“we”, “us” or “our”) collection, use, storage, sharing and protection of your personal information. It applies to our website and all related sites, applications, services and tools regardless of how you access or use them. This Privacy Policy will help you understand how we use your information and what we do with it.  

We respect the privacy of our online visitors and registered users (“Users”) as such we will take reasonable steps to protect your information.

**1.About Us**

Paystack is an online payment platform that makes it easy for merchants to accept credit and debit card payments online from customers. 

**2\. Updates, Modifications & Amendments**

We may need to update, modify or amend our privacy policy as our technology evolves. We reserve the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to Users on this page. 

We advise that you check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification on the page If a User objects to any of the changes to the Policy, the User must cease using this Site, or terminate account in the event an account has been created.

**3\. Age Restriction**

Our website and services are not directed to children under 18. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 18. If as a parent or guardian, you become aware that your child or ward child has provided us with any information without your consent, please contact us through details on this Privacy Policy.  

**4\. The Information we Collect**

  **4.1 Personal Information**

To gain full access to our website and services, you must register for a Paystack account. When you register for an account, we collect Personal Information which you voluntarily provide to us.

Personal Information refers to the personal information you submit, when you sign up or any information that can be used to identify or contact you, (e.g. email address, password, name, telephone no and business name). It may also include anonymous information that is linked you specifically, (e.g., IP Address). 

 We use your Personal Information to:

  1. provide you with the required services.
  2. respond to your questions or requests
  3. improve Paystack’s operations
  4. address inappropriate use of our website
  5. prevent, detect and manage risk against fraud and illegal activities 
  6. target advertisements, newsletter and service updates 
  7. verify the information that you provide with third parties
  8. update our database, improve content and website layout
  9. resolve disputes that may arise

We may retrieve additional Personal Information about you from third parties and other identification/verification services such as your financial Institution, payment processor and verification services. With your consent, we may also collect additional Personal Information in other ways including emails, surveys, and other forms of communication. Once you begin using our services through your Paystack account we will keep records of your transactions and collect information of your other activities related to our services. We will not share or disclose your Personal Information with a third party without your consent. 

**4.2 Information that we collect from website visitors**

We do not collect your Personal Information when you visit the website. However, so we can monitor and improve our website and services we may collect non-personally-identifiable information. We will not share or disclose this information with third parties except as a necessary part of providing our website and services. We may use the information to target advertisements to you.  

**4.3 Information that we collect from test users**

When you test our services using the “Demo” part of our website, we collect both non-personally identifiable information and personally identifiable information. Information we collect include your IP address, information about your computer, and other standard web log information to monitor the test transactions. We also collect your email address and credit card information you provide to conduct the test transactions. We will not share and disclose your credit card information. ** **

**4.4 Information that we collect from checkout users**

When you checkout with Paystack on a merchant’s website, we collect and store your payment card information, your email address, your mobile phone number, and billing and shipping address.

We may share your contact information with merchants as part of your purchase details for record purposes. We will not share this information with other third parties except as a necessary part of providing our website and services. We do not share your card information with merchants. Please review your merchant’s privacy policy to understand the privacy policies guiding the merchant you transact with. 

**5\. Cookies**

We use cookies to identify you as a User and make your user experience easier, customise our services, content and advertising; help you ensure that your account security is not compromised, mitigate risk and prevent fraud; and to promote trust and safety on our website. Cookies allow our servers to remember your account log-in information when you visit our website, IP addresses, date and time of visits, monitor web traffic and prevent fraudulent activities. If your browser or browser add-on permits, you have the choice to disable cookies on our website, however this may limit your ability to use our website. 

**6.How we protect your Information**

Paystack is committed to managing your Personal Information in line with global industry best practices. We protect your Personal Information using physical, technical, and administrative security measures to reduce the risks of loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure and alteration, we also use industry-standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology to safeguard your Personal Information. Other security safeguards include but are not limited to data encryption, firewalls, and physical access controls to our building and files and only granting access to Personal Information to only employees who require it to fulfil their job responsibilities. 

**7.How we share the Personal Information you provide  **

To enable us render our services to you on our website, we may share your information with trusted third parties, such third parties include financial institutions, payment processors verification services, as well as any third parties that you have directly authorized to receive your Personal Information. Your Personal Information may be stored in locations outside the direct control of Paystack, for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers.

We may disclose your Personal Information compliance with applicable law or a legal obligation to which we are bound. 

Please note that merchants, sellers, and Users you buy from or contract with have their own privacy policies, and although Paystack’s Merchant Terms of Use does not allow the other transacting party to use this information for anything other than as authorised by you, Paystack is not responsible for their actions, including their information protection practices.

The use of your information by such third party will be subject to their applicable privacy policy, which you should carefully review.

**8\. The Data that we Retain**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you with our services, comply with our legal and statutory obligations or verify your information with a financial institution. 

Paystack is statutory obligated to retain the data you provide us with in order to process transactions, ensure settlements, make refunds, identify fraud and in compliance with laws and regulatory guidelines applicable to us, our banking providers and credit card processors.

Therefore, even after closing your Paystack account, we will retain certain data to comply with these obligations. 

**11.Contact Information**

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us through any of the details provided below:

Email: hello@paystack.com

Telephone No: +234 908 566 2909
